Guide to the Robert Penn Warren Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1922-88; Series I; 40; (95 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Welty, Eudora, 1941-84 (Box 77, Folder 1518-19)
    - Wescott, Glenway, 1950-77 (Box 77, Folder 1520-21)
    - Wesleyan College (Georgia), 1959-60 (Box 77, Folder 1522)
    - Wesleyan University, 1945-70 (Box 77, Folder 1523-24)
    - West, Ray B., Jr., 1947-77 (Box 77, Folder 1525)
      See also: Rocky Mountain Review
    - West, William W., 1964 (Box 77, Folder 1526)
    - Westendorp, Tjebbe, 1966-84 (Box 77, Folder 1527-28)
    - Western Kentucky University, 1982-87 (Box 78, Folder 1529)
    - Westminster Magazine, 1934 (Box 78, Folder 1530)
    - Weston, John, 1965-67 (Box 78, Folder 1531)
    - Wheelock, John Hall
      See: Scribner's Sons, Box 63, folder 1253
    - White, George Abbott, 1974-81 (Box 78, Folder 1532)
    - White, Victor, 1958-79 (Box 78, Folder 1533)
    - Whitehall, Harold, 1947-58 (Box 78, Folder 1534)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1975-83 (Box 78, Folder 1535)
    - Whittimore, Reed ( Furioso ), 1947-48, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 1536)
      See also: New Republic, Box 50, folder 984
    - Wilbur, Richard, 1954-81 (Box 78, Folder 1537)
    - Wilcox, Jim, 1981-85 (Box 78, Folder 1538)
    - Wilder, Amos N., 1957-75 (Box 78, Folder 1539)
    - Wilder, Thornton Wilder, Isabel, 1952-72 (Box 78, Folder 1540)
    - William Morris Agency, 1940-55 (Box 78, Folder 1541-48)
      See also: Helen Strauss, Box 67, folder 1340
    - William Morris Agency, 1956-63 (Box 79, Folder 1549-62)
    - William Morris Agency, 1964-71 (Box 80, Folder 1563-73)
    - William Morris Agency, 1972-88 (Box 81, Folder 1574-87)
    - Williams, Alice Owen, 1980, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 1588)
    - Williams (Bowen), Joan, 1961-81 (Box 81, Folder 1589)
    - Williams, Oscar, 1940-64, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 1590)
    - Williams, Tennessee, 1945 Jul 16 (Box 82, Folder 1591)
    - Williams College, 1945-66 (Box 82, Folder 1592)
    - Williams International Assembly, 1958-59 (Box 82, Folder 1593)
    - Wills, Jesse, 1966-77 (Box 82, Folder 1594-97)
    - Wilson, Edmund Wilson, Elena, 1942-74 (Box 82, Folder 1598)
      See also: New York Times Review of Books, Box 50, folder 1003
    - Wilson, Sloan
    - Wimsatt, William Wimsatt, Margaret, 1953-78 (Box 82, Folder 1599)
    - Winnick, Roy H., 1980-81, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 1600)
    - Winters, Yvor, 1931, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 1601)
    - Wirtz, Warren, 1945-48 (Box 82, Folder 1602)
    - Wisconsin, University of, 1947-65 (Box 82, Folder 1603)
    - Wise, K. Kelly, 1980-83, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 1604)
    - Wittenberg, Lester Jr., 1962-63 (Box 82, Folder 1605)
    - Wojtnik, Ted, 1980-82 (Box 82, Folder 1606)
      See also: Katherine Anne Porter, Box 56, folder 1113
    - Wood, Nancy Tate, 1969-81 (Box 82, Folder 1607)
    - Woodman, Herbert B., 1960-78, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 1608)
    - Woodward, C. Vann, 1954-83 (Box 82, Folder 1609-12)
    - Wouk, Herman, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 1613)
    - The Writers' Conference in the Rocky Mountains
      See: Edward Davison, Box 19, folder 403
    - Wyoming Council on the Arts, 1971-83 (Box 82, Folder 1614)
    - "Y" general, 1957-84 (Box 83, Folder 1615)
    - Yaddo, 1952-74 (Box 83, Folder 1616)
    - Yale University
      - Academic Departments (General), 1961-70 (Box 83, Folder 1617)
      - American Studies Program, 1965-79 (Box 83, Folder 1618)
      - Department of English, 1956-77 (Box 83, Folder 1619)
      - Elizabethan Club, 1951-61 (Box 83, Folder 1620)
      - Libraries, 1950-81 (Box 83, Folder 1621-35)
      - Libraries, 1983-87 (Box 84, Folder 1636-38)
      - News Bureau, 1950-62 (Box 84, Folder 1639)
      - Publications, 1951-77, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 1640)
      - Residential Colleges, 1956-83 (Box 84, Folder 1641)
      - School of Drama, 1949-76 (Box 84, Folder 1642)
      - Student Organizations, 1952-81 (Box 84, Folder 1643-44)
      - General, 1947-77, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 1645-46)
    - Yale University Press, 1964-83 (Box 84, Folder 1647)
    - Young, Philip, 1951-52 (Box 84, Folder 1648)
    - Young, Stark, 1935-60 (Box 84, Folder 1649-51)
    - Young, Thomas Daniel, 1967-76 (Box 84, Folder 1652)
    - Yount, John, 1968-79 (Box 84, Folder 1653)
    - "Z" general, 1948-80 (Box 85, Folder 1654)
    - Zabel, Morton D., 1931-63 (Box 85, Folder 1655-56)
    - Zemplany, Bela, 1965 Oct 9 (Box 85, Folder 1657)
    - Zhenzhen, Lin, 1984-86 (Box 85, Folder 1658)
    - Zielinski, Bronislaw, 1960-72, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 1659)
    - Zinn, Howard, 1965 Feb 15 (Box 85, Folder 1660)
    - Unidentified, 1928-59 (Box 86, Folder 1661-76)
    - Unidentified, 1960-81 (Box 87, Folder 1677-88)
    - Unidentified, 1982-87, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 1689-94)
    - Fan Mail, 1943-62 (Box 88, Folder 1695-98)
    - Fan Mail, 1963-75 (Box 89, Folder 1699-1705)
    - Fan Mail, 1976-86, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 1706-15)
  - PUBLISHERS CORRESPONDENCE
    - Collins Publishers, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 1716)
    - Eurographica, 1984-87 (Box 91, Folder 1717)
    - Eyre & Spottiswoode, Ltd., 1949-64, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 1718)
    - Harcourt & Brace, 1932-63 (Box 91, Folder 1719-27)
    - Harcourt & Brace, 1964-79 (Box 92, Folder 1728-33)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1977-87 (Box 92, Folder 1734)
    - Harper & Row, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 1735)
    - Holt Publishers, 1936-75 (Box 92, Folder 1736-39)
    - Houghton Mifflin, 1933-82 (Box 92, Folder 1740)
    - Little, Brown & Company, 1935-80 (Box 92, Folder 1741)
    - Martin, Secker & Warburg, Ltd., 1971-76 (Box 92, Folder 1742-43)
    - Martin, Secker & Warburg, Ltd., 1977-84 (Box 93, Folder 1744)
    - Payson & Clarke, Ltd., 1928-29 (Box 93, Folder 1745)
    - Prentice-Hall, 1960-78, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 1746-47)
    - Pressworks, 1979-81 (Box 93, Folder 1748)
    - Random House, 1947-59 (Box 93, Folder 1749-54)
    - Random House, 1960-73 (Box 94, Folder 1755-67)
    - Random House, 1974-88, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1768-72)
    - Random House (business), 1950-72, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1773)
    - Reynal & Hitchcock, 1941-65 (Box 95, Folder 1774)
    - St. Martin's Press, 1956-73 (Box 95, Folder 1775-76)
    - Wright, Stuart (Palemon Press), 1977-88, n.d. (Box 95, Folder 1777-83)
- Writings, 1930-85; Series II; 60; (145 boxes)
  Series II, Writings, is divided into Books and Shorter Works. Books, which include book-length works co-authored or edited by Warren, are arranged alphabetically. Shorter Works include poems, short plays, essays, and reviews as well as transcripts of speeches and lectures, interviews, and panel discussions. Titles are arranged alphabetically within these subdivisions.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 333-334 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult access services for further information.
  - BOOKS
    - All the King's Men
      - Proud Flesh
        - Holograph worksheets, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1784-85)
        - Draft A: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1786-87)
        - Draft B: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1788-89)
        - Draft C: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1790-91)
        - Draft D: typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1792-93)
        - with copy of letter to Kenneth Burke
        - Draft E: typescript, corrected (with revision sheets), n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1794-95)
        - Draft F: typescript, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1796-97)
        - Draft G: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1798-99)
        - Draft H: typescript, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 1800-01)
        - Draft I: typescript, with holograph notes, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1802)
        - Draft J: typescript, corrected, 1946-47 (Box 97, Folder 1803)
        - Draft K: typescript, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1804)
        - Draft L: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1805-06)
        - Draft M: typescript, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1807-08)
        - Draft N (incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1809)
        - Draft O (incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1810)
        - Draft P (incomplete): typescript, with letter and comments by Francis Fergusson., [1941] (Box 97, Folder 1811)
        - Draft fragment (with Warren's note, "This was first fragment written for Proud Flesh ...."): holograph, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1812)
        - Various early draft fragments: typescripts, corrected, n.d. (Box 97, Folder 1813-15)
      - All the King's Men
        - Introduction to the Modern Library edition: printed text, photocopies, [1953] (Box 98, Folder 1816)
        - "Introduction to Time edition" (Marked "First version"): typescript, corrected, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 1817)
        - Introduction to English edition
          - Typescript, carbon, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 1818)
          - Page proofs, photocopy (with letter), 1973 (Box 98, Folder 1819)
        - Introduction to Franklin Library edition: typescript and galley proofs (with letter), 1977 (Box 98, Folder 1820-21)
        - Introduction to Book-of-the-Month Club Thirty-fifth Aniversary Edition
          - First draft: holograph, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1822)
          - Second draft: typescript, corrected and carbons (with correspondence), 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1823-26)
          - "Fourth version"
          - Typescript A, corrected, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1827)
          - Typescript B, corrected, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1828)
          - Typescript C, corrected, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1829)
          - Page proofs, corrected, [1981] (Box 98, Folder 1830)
          - New York Times reprint: galley proofs, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1831)
        - Prefatory note for This Is My Best, ed. Whit Burnett, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 1832)
        - Notes and worksheets: holograph (Box 98, Folder 1833-34)
        - "End of All the King's Men " (first draft?): holograph, 1945 (Box 98, Folder 1835)
        - Manuscript pages, marked 50-52 (first draft?): holograph, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 1836)
        - Draft A: typescript, corrected (with paste-overs), n.d. (Box 99, Folder 1837-54)
        - Draft B (incomplete?): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 1855-66)
        - Manuscript fragments (miscellaneous pages): typescript and carbons (Box 100, Folder 1867)
        - "Rejected first chapter" (with other cancelled pages): typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 1868)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, 1946 (Box 101, Folder 1869-76)
        - Page proofs (lacking pp. 171-200)
          See: Oversize, Box 281, folders 5162-64
        - Omnibook Magazine (abridgment), 1946 Dec (Box 102, Folder 1877)
        - "'All the King's Men': The Matrix of Experience": photocopy, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 1878)
        - Publicity: typescripts and printed texts, 1946, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1879)
          See: Oversize, Box 283, folders 5168-69
        - Reviews and commentaries, 1946-71 (Box 102, Folder 1880-84)
        - Critical Studies
          - Alter, Robert. "The American Political Novel." New York Times Book Review, 1980 Aug 10 (Box 102, Folder 1885)
          - Brooks, Cleanth. " All the King's Men: The Local and the Universal": typescript (Box 102, Folder 1886)
          - Friedman, Richard. "The Attitude of American Politics." HIKA (Kenyon College), 1956 (Box 102, Folder 1887)
          - Grimshaw, James A., Jr. "Robert Penn Warren's All the King's Men: An Annotated Checklist of Criticism": typescript, 1975 Jan 6 (Box 102, Folder 1888)
          - Grimshaw, James A., Jr. " All the King's Men: A Critique of the Criticism": typescript, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 1889)
          - Hagemann, E.R. "Chronology of All the King's Men ": typescript, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1890)
          - Konikkara, Sister Cleopatra. "Robert Penn Warren's All the King's Men ." Literary Studies (offprint), n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1891)
          - Pease, Dexter. "God Have Mercy on the Mariner: A Coleridgean Reading of 'All the King's Men'." The Drew Gateway, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 1892)
          - Sillars, Malcolm O. "Warren's All the King's Men: A Study in Populism." The American Quarterly (offprint), n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1893)
          - Stein, Arnold. Untitled essay on All the King's Men: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1894)
          - Vauthier, Simone. "The Case of the Vanishing Narrator: An Inquiry into All the King's Men ." The Southern Literary Journal: photocopy, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 1895)
          - Wilson, Mary Ann T. "Search for the Eternal Present: Absalom, Absalom and All the King's Men ." The Connecticut Review., 1974 Oct (Box 102, Folder 1896)
          - Winchell, Mark. Chapter of untitled dissertation: typescript, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1897)
        - Miscellaneous, 1950-89, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 1898-99)
      - All the King's Men (film adaptation)
        - Reviews, 1948-53 (Box 102, Folder 1900-01)
        - Scrapbook
          See: Oversize, Box 282, folder 5167
        - Boxoffice Blue Ribbon Award (with commentary and letter), 1950 (Box 102, Folder 1902)
        - Miscellaneous, 1947-66 (Box 102, Folder 1903)
      - All the King's Men (drama)
        - Preface to unidentified dramatic version: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1904)
        - Introduction to Italian translation: holograph and typescript (Box 103, Folder 1905)
        - Dramatic Workshop Production (Erwin Piscator)
          See also: Erwin Piscator (Box 55, folder 1093)
          - Mixed early drafts (marked "worksheets"): typescripts, corrected, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1906-10)
          - Draft A: typescript, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1911-12)
          - Draft B: typescript, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 1913-14)
        - Later revised versions
          - Draft A (with changes and comments by Aaron Frankel): typescript, [1954] (Box 103, Folder 1915-16)
          - Draft B
          - Typescript, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1917)
          - Photocopy (marked "old version"), n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1918)
          - Draft C (two copies, with different pagination): typescript, carbons, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1919-20)
        - 74th Street Theatre versions
          - "First Working Text for Production, 74th St. Theatre": typescript, corrected, 1959 (Box 104, Folder 1921-22)
          - "Prompt script": typescript and carbons, corrected, [1959] (Box 104, Folder 1923)
        - Drama programs and announcements, 1946-87, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1924-6)
          See also: Oversize, Box 282, folder 5166
        - Reviews, 1947-87, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1927-34)
        - Polish theatre productions: publicity, programs, and photographs, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 1935)
        - 74th Street Theatre production: photographs
          See: Oversize, Box 281, folder 5165
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1936)
      - Willie Stark: His Rise and Fall
        - Draft A: typescript, corrected, 1955 (Box 105, Folder 1937-38)
        - Draft B: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 1939-41)
        - Draft C (marked "version done at the Margo Jones Theatre, Dallas... 1958"): typescript, carbon (Box 105, Folder 1942-44)
        - Draft D: typescript, corrected (unknown hand) (Box 105, Folder 1945-48)
        - Draft E (marked "old version"): typescript, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1949-52)
        - Draft F: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1953-58)
        - Draft G (marked "director's copy" [Aaron Frankel]): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 106, Folder 1959-62)
        - Draft H: typescript, carbon, corrected (with stage directions in an unknown hand [Frankel?]) (Box 106, Folder 1963-66)
    - American Literature: The Makers and the Making
      - Early drafts of prefaces by Warren: holograph and typescript (Box 107, Folder 1967-89)
      - Early drafts of prefaces by Warren: holograph and typescript (Box 108, Folder 1990-2011)
      - Early drafts of prefaces by Warren: holograph and typescript (Box 109, Folder 2012-16)
      - Printed text, photocopy, corrected (incomplete; pages eliminated for revised edition), n.d. (Box 109, Folder 2017-29)
      - Printed text, photocopy, corrected (incomplete; pages eliminated for revised edition), n.d. (Box 110, Folder 2030-44)
      - Printed text, photocopy, corrected (incomplete; pages eliminated for revised edition), n.d. (Box 111, Folder 2045-62)
      - Printed text, photocopy, corrected (incomplete; pages eliminated for revised edition), n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2063-67)
      - Incomplete text (pp.1197-1623: printed text, photocopy, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2068-76)
      - General introduction by Cleanth Brooks: typescript, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2077)
      - Promotional brochure, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2078)
      - Reviews (Box 112, Folder 2079)
    - An Anthology of Stories from the Southern Review
      - Reviews, 1953-54 (Box 112, Folder 2080)
    - The Apple Tree
      - Summary (mistakenly marked God's Own Time by Warren): typescript, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2081)
      - Typescript, corrected (chapter 8 missing), [c. 1930-32] (Box 113, Folder 2082-87)
    - An Approach to Literature:
      - "Notes on An Approach to Literature ": printed text., 1975 (Box 113, Folder 2088)
      - Promotional material, [1975] (Box 113, Folder 2089)
    - At Heaven's Gate
      - Synopsis: typescript, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2090)
      - Draft A ("first draft": chapters I-V only): typescript, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2091-92)
      - Draft B: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2093-96)
      - Draft B: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2097-2100)
      - "Statement of Ashby Wyndham" (Ashby Wyndham sections): typescript (Box 114, Folder 2101)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2102-11)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2112-14)
      - Setting typescript ("English Edition": front matter only), n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2115)
      - Author's proof (incomplete), n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2116)
      - Dust jacket, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2117)
      - Photo of dust jacket for New Directions edition, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2118)
      - Promotional material, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2119)
      - Reviews, 1943-85, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2120)
      - Critical studies
        - Langly, John L., Jr. "At Heaven's Gate: A Preface": typescript, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2121)
    - Audubon
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2122)
      - Draft A (sections I-V): holograph, [1969] (Box 115, Folder 2123)
      - Draft B (early draft, incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2124)
      - Draft C (revised draft, incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2125)
      - Draft D: typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2126)
      - Draft E (later draft: sections IV, V only): holograph and typescript (Box 115, Folder 2127)
      - Draft F (sections IV-VI): typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2128)
      - Setting typescript, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2129)
      - Corrections (headnotes and inserts), 1969 Jul 9 (Box 115, Folder 2130)
      - Page proofs (with letters)
        See: Oversize, box 284, folder 5170-72
      - Revision lists, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 2131)
      - Advertising schedules, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 2132)
      - Random House editorial material, 1969-70 (Box 115, Folder 2133)
      - Binding sample and jacket covers (Box 115, Folder 2134)
      - Reviews, 1969-70 (Box 115, Folder 2135-36)
      - Critical studies
        - Clark, William Bedford. "Warren's, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2137)
        - Audubon: The Artist as Hero." South Atlantic Quarterly (offprint, with annotations by Warren)
        - Drake, Robert. "Tell Me a Story: A Note on Modern Southern Literature": typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2138)
        - Goldstein, Laurence. "Audubon and R. P. Warren: To See and Record All Life": photocopy (Box 115, Folder 2139)
      - New Yorker excerpt
        - Typescripts (incomplete, with related correspondence), 1969 (Box 115, Folder 2140)
        - Setting typescript (with related correspondence), 1969, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 2141)
        - Author's proofs, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 2142)
        - Related Correspondence, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 2143)
        - Miscellaneous, 1978-79 (Box 115, Folder 2144)
    - Band of Angels
      - Source material (notes and notebooks) (Box 116, Folder 2145-46)
      - Holograph notes and worksheet (Box 116, Folder 2147-50)
      - Early draft fragment (from chapter V): typescript, n.d. (Box 116, Folder 2151)
      - Early draft fragments (marked "retyped pages"): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 116, Folder 2152)
      - Draft B: typescript and holograph, corrected (Box 116, Folder 2155-62)
      - Draft B: typescript and holograph, corrected (Box 117, Folder 2163-75)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 284, folders 5173-76
      - Author's proofs
        - Copy I
          See: Oversize, Box 284, folders 5177-81
        - Copy II
          See: Oversize, Box 285, folders 5182-86
      - Plate proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 285, folders 5187-90
      - Plate proofs (incomplete set)
        See: Oversize, Box 285, folder 5191
      - Publicity, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 2177)
        See also: Oversize, Box 285, folder 5191a
      - Reviews, 1955-84 (Box 118, Folder 2178-83)
      - Reviews (film), 1957 (Box 118, Folder 2184)
      - Viewpoint: Band of Angels, broadcast over Mutual Broadcasting Network, Station WOK NYC, 1965 June 5-6; 1; 00:14:26; Static can be heard on the audiotape reel. The program is distorted at times. (Box 333, Item barcode 39002091249731)
        Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Being Here ("Life Is a Fable")
      - Early compilations: typescripts and carbons, 1979, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2185-89)
      - Draft A (incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 2190)
      - Draft B (revised poems): holograph and typescripts, corrected (Box 118, Folder 2191-92)
      - Draft C (marked "3rd revision"), n.d. (Box 119, Folder 2193-95)
      - Draft D (marked "4th revision"): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 119, Folder 2196-2200)
      - Draft E (marked "5th version"): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 119, Folder 2201)
      - Draft F (marked "6th revision"): typescript, n.d. (Box 119, Folder 2202-05)
      - Draft G (later draft): typescript, carbon (Box 119, Folder 2206-08)
      - Draft H (with comments by Harold Bloom): typescript, n.d. (Box 119, Folder 2209)
      - Draft H (with comments by Harold Bloom): typescript, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2210)
      - Draft I (marked "Final texts, extra-1980"): typescript (incomplete?) (Box 120, Folder 2211)
      - Critique by William Meredith, 1979 Jul 2 (Box 120, Folder 2212)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, 1979 (Box 120, Folder 2213-15)
      - Galley proofs (marked "Master Set")
        See: Oversize, Box 286, folder 5192
      - Galley proofs (marked "Author's Marked Set")
        See: Oversize, Box 286, folders 5193-94
      - Page proofs (marked "Master Set")
        See: Oversize, Box 286, folders 5195-97
      - Page proofs (retouched)
        See: Oversize, box 286, folders 5198-5200
      - Reproduction proofs (incomplete), 1980 (Box 120, Folder 2216)
      - "Blues", n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2217)
      - Editorial material, 1979-80 (Box 120, Folder 2218)
      - Editorial correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 120, Folder 2219)
      - Reviews, 1980-83 (Box 120, Folder 2220-21)
      - Critical studies (Box 120, Folder 2222)
        - Stitt, Peter. "Life's Instancy and the Astrolabe of Joy." Typescript, corrected., 1980
    - Brother to Dragons: A Tale in Verse and Voices
      - First version
        - Source material, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2223)
        - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2224)
        - Draft A (First Draft): holograph, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2225-29)
        - Draft B (Box 121, Folder 2230-36)
          - Copy 1: original typescript, corrected, n.d.